A Guide to the Social Science Research Council records, Soviet Studies, Record Group 3, Series 6 FA1486
Rockefeller Archive Center
Social Science Research Council records, Soviet Studies, Record Group 3, Series 6
1978-1996
Rockefeller Archive Center
Social Science Research Council
FA1486
88.4 Cubic Feet
Arrangement
The Social Science Research Council archives are arranged into three record groups distinguished by the date of their donation to the Archive Center. Accession 1 (Record Group 1) consists of the documents received by the Archive Center in 1990; Accession 2 (Record Group 2) was transferred to the Archive Center in 1994; Record Group 3 was transferred to the Archive Center in 2017-2018.
SSRC, RG 3, Series 6, Soviet Studies, is divided into four subseries: 1. Programs and Development; 2. Fellowship Records and Institutional Support; 3. Fellowship Records - Declinations (Graduate Training, Dissertation, and Postdoctoral); and 4. JCSSS and Eurasian Program.
These subseries divisions were created in the course of processing in order to facilitate access to the materials. There is overlap between subseries, however, and the divisions are not always exact.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Social Science Research Council donated its records to the Rockefeller Archive Center as an unrestricted gift by Certificate of Gift dated December 17-21, 2015.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
When requesting audiovisual material, please refer to the Title and the AV Number (example: AV 1916). Researchers are asked to check the "Restrictions" note for each Title. If a Title does not currently have an access copy, please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
Scope and Contents
The Soviet Studies series of SSRC, RG 3, Series 6, documents the activities of the Joint Committee on Soviet Studies (JCSS), later known as the Joint Committee on the Soviet Union and its Successor States (JCSSS), and its associated subcommittees. The records consist of meeting materials, minutes, and correspondence; funding inquiries and applications; subcommittee records relating to meetings, membership, and workshops and conferences (presentations and planning); and especially materials stemming from and concerning the administration of fellowships and other awards programs.
- Programs and Development, 1980-1994; 1
  Scope and Contents
  The Programs and Development subseries documents the establishment and operation of the Joint Committee on Soviet Studies from the early 1980s to around 1994. It contains records of its meetings from 1983-1991 and chronological files from 1987-1993. The subseries includes correspondence and requests for funding from foundations, the National Endowment for the Humanities, and especially for program funding from the U.S. Department of State, through the Soviet-Eastern European Research and Training Act of 1983 (Title VIII).
  The JCSS established several subcommittees to advance field development in Soviet Studies. This subseries includes the records of these committees and, in particular, of their meetings, conferences, workshops, and other activities.
  - Joint Committee on Soviet Studies (JCSS) - Formation and Membership, 1982-1984, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Joint Committee on Soviet Studies (JCSS) - Membership, 1982-1988 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Joint Committee on Soviet Studies (JCSS) - Background Materials, 1980-1984 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Joint Committee on Soviet Studies (JCSS) - Meeting, 1983 March 4-5 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Joint Committee on Soviet Studies (JCSS) - Meeting, 1983 May 20-21 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Includes correspondence and memos, May-December 1983, and notes on Executive Committee meeting in September 1983.
  - Joint Committee on Soviet Studies (JCSS) - Meeting, 1983 September 30 - October 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Joint Committee on Soviet Studies (JCSS) - Meeting, 1984 February 10-11 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Joint Committee on Soviet Studies (JCSS) - Meeting, 1984 May (Box 1, Folder 8)
    No minutes or meeting information in file.
  - Joint Committee on Soviet Studies (JCSS) - Meeting, 1984 November 10-11 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Joint Committee on Soviet Studies (JCSS) - Meeting, 1985 April 12-13 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Joint Committee on Soviet Studies (JCSS) - Meeting, 1985 June 3 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Joint Committee on Soviet Studies (JCSS) - Meeting, 1985 November 24-25 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Joint Committee on Soviet Studies (JCSS) - Meeting, 1986 April 5-6 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Joint Committee on Soviet Studies (JCSS) - Meeting, 1986 October 17-18 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Joint Committee on Soviet Studies (JCSS) - Meeting, 1987 April 3-4 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Joint Committee on Soviet Studies (JCSS) - Meeting, 1987 October 16-17 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Joint Committee on Soviet Studies (JCSS) - Meeting, 1988 March 18-19 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Joint Committee on Soviet Studies (JCSS) - Meeting, 1989 April 21-22 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    File includes undated draft minutes of the September 30 - October 1, 1988 meeting of the JCSS.
  - Joint Committee on Soviet Studies (JCSS) - Meeting, 1990 November 2-3 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Joint Committee on Soviet Studies (JCSS) - Budget Report, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Report on expenditures of grant funds for Research Planning and Fellowship Awards.
  - Joint Committee on Soviet Studies (JCSS) - Workshop and Publication Notices (for "Items"), 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Joint Committee on Soviet Studies (JCSS) - Soviet and East European Agriculture Proposal, 1986-1989 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Joint Committee on Soviet Studies - International Fellowship Program for the Development of Soviet Studies, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    Correspondence concerning establishment of the Rockefeller Foundation - funded program.
  - Joint Committee on Soviet Studies - Politics of Culture in Early Modern Russia Workshop Proposal, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Nancy Kollmann proposal for workshop to be held in June 1990.
  - Joint Committee on Soviet Studies - Technological Innovation in China and the Soviet Union Workshop Proposal, circa 1988 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Joint Committee on Soviet Studies - Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Includes memos concerning IREX and Soviet graduate student program, 1990. Also includes Andrew Walder correspondence and paper for conference on "Political Consequences of Departures from Central Planning," funded by the Joint Committee on Eastern Europe.
  - Joint Committee on Soviet Studies - Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    Correspondence and memos by Robert Huber and others. Includes funding inquiries; renaming of the JCSS; Conference on the Future Direction of Soviet Studies in the Social Sciences, 1992; Backlog Grants panel, 1992; comments on the draft report of the JACIP Panel on Soviet Studies, 1991; memo on IREX priorities; dissolution of subcommittees.
  - Joint Committee on Soviet Studies - Area Studies and SSRC Strategic Planning, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    Memos to David Featherman by Robert Huber and JCSS members on importance of area studies to SSRC program.
  - Joint Committee on Soviet Studies - First Five Years of Perestroika Conference Proposal, 1990 March 8-9 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    File includes paper by Robert T. Huber on "Perestroika and U.S.-Soviet Relations: The Five-Year Plan No One Devised."
  - Joint Committee on Soviet Studies - Politics and Personnel, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    Joint Advisory Committee on International Programs (JACIP) memos concerning JCSS membership and name change. Robert Huber, Jerry Hough, and Brian Silver correspondence concerning Domestic Politics committee leadership and direction.
  - Joint Committee on Soviet Studies - Transnational and Comparative Studies - Proposals, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    Proposals for collaborative grants for research planning.
  - Joint Committee on Soviet Studies - Wingspread Conference on the Future of Soviet Studies (Cancelled), 1992 July 16-20 (Box 3, Folder 32-33)
    Conference to be sponsored by the Johnson Foundation was postponed because key participants were unable to attend.
  - Joint Committee on Soviet Studies - Social Sciences in Russia, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 34-35)
    Memo to the Carnegie Corporation on ways the SSRC could aid the social sciences in Russia and the former Soviet Union. File also includes correspondence with the Ford Foundation, the Soros Foundation, and the MacArthur Foundation (for history projects), and a report on a March 1992 workshop at the National Academy of Sciences.
  - Joint Committee on Soviet Studies - National Academy of Sciences Working Group, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    Stanley Heginbotham report on January 1993 trip to Moscow, meetings, and correspondence, concerning efforts to revitalize social sciences in the former Soviet Union. Trip sponsored by the National Research Council.
  - JCSS - Joint Advisory Committee on International Programs (JACIP), 1984, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - JCSS - Joint Advisory Committee on International Programs (JACIP) - JCSS Review, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - JCSS/JCSSS - Joint Advisory Committee on International Programs (JACIP), 1992-1995 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - JCSS - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH) - Proposal for Supplemental Funding, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    For support of activities of newly formed Joint Committee on Soviet Studies; as supplement to grant for International Research Program of the ACLS-SSRC.
  - JCSS - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH) - Proposal, 1985 - 1986 Decenber (Box 4, Folder 41)
    For funding of the joint area committees.
  - JCSS - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH) - Proposal, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - JCSS - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH) - Proposal, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - JCSS - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH) - Proposal (for 1989), 1988 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    For support of international postdoctoral grants programs, 1989-1991.
  - Title VIII - Legislation, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    Copies of Copies of the Congressional Record pertaining to the passage of the Soviet - East European Research and Training Act of 1983 (Title VIII of the Department of State Authorization Act, for fiscal years 1984 and 1985). Also known as the Lugar - Biden bill.
  - Title VIII - Consortium Activities, 1983-1987 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    General file concerning applications for funding under Title VIII; contains drafts of proposal sections. In addition to the JCSS, the Title VIII Consortium included the Joint Committee on Eastern Europe, the International Research and Exchanges Board (IREX), the Kennan Institute of Advanced Russian Studies, and the National Council for Soviet and East European Research (NCSEER).
  - JCSS - Title VIII - Correspondence, 1984-1985 June (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - JCSS - Title VIII - Correspondence, 1985 July - 1986 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - JCSS - Title VIII - Application (for 1986), 1985 October 7 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - JCSS - Title VIII - Correspondence, 1984 - 1986 July (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - JCSS - Title VIII - Application (for 1987), 1986 September 15 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - JCSS - Title VIII - Correspondence, 1986-1987 February (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - JCSS - Title VIII - Correspondence, 1987 March-September (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - JCSS - Title VIII - Application (for 1988), 1987 September 30 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - JCSS - Title VIII - Application (for 1989), 1988 September (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - JCSS - Title VIII - Application (for 1989), 1988 September; 5 1/4 floppy disk. (Box 6, Folder 55)
    Disk contents unknown.
    Conditions Governing Access
    Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
  - JCSS - Title VIII - Correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - JCSS - Title VIII - Fellowship and Research Grant Accounting, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    General file. Includes attachments from FY 1988 application, fellowship lists, and various budget reports.
  - JCSS - International Research and Exchanges Board (IREX), 1989 (Box 6, Folder 58)
    Correspondence concerning support for JCSS Sociology projects.
  - JCSS - Mellon Foundation - Correspondence and Proposals, 1983-1988 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    Includes drafts of 1983 and 1987 proposals.
  - JCSS - Mellon Foundation - Proposal, 1987 September-October (Box 6, Folder 60)
    Renewal of funding for Research Planning and Fellowship Support for five years, 1989-1993.
  - JCSS - Ford Foundation - Comparative Legislatures Conference Proposal, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    Draft proposal for two conferences, to be held in Washington, DC, and Moscow, 1990-1991, on the comparative study of the American and Soviet legislatures.
  - JCSS - Ford Foundation - Soviet and East European Economics Workshops, 1984-1986 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    Proposals and reports for partial funding of Summer Workshops, 1985-1989.
  - JCSS - Ford Foundation - Soviet and East European Economics Workshops, 1986-1989, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - JCSS - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation - Soviet and East European Economics Workshops, 1987-1989 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    Funding for Summer Workshops, 1988-1990.
  - JCSS - Carnegie Corporation - Domestic Politics Workshops - Correspondence, 1987-1989, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - JCSS - Carnegie Corporation - Domestic Politics Workshops - Proposal (for 1988 and 1989), 1987 August (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - JCSS - Carnegie Corporation - Domestic Politics Workshop - Report, 1988 June 5-17 (Box 7, Folder 67)
    Summer Workshop on Soviet Domestic Politics and Society, University of Toronto. Report includes Questionnaire responses.
  - JCSS - Carnegie Corporation - Domestic Politics Workshops - Final Report, 1989 August (Box 7, Folder 68)
    Summer Workshops on Soviet Domestic Politics and Society, University of Toronto, June 1988 and 1989. Report includes Questionnaire responses from 1989 workshop.
  - Pew Charitable Trust, 1990 October 30 (Box 7, Folder 69)
    Memo on SSRC meeting with Pew staff concerning environmental programs.
  - JCSS - Rockefeller Foundation - Foreign Policy Dual Seminar, 1983-1985 (Box 7, Folder 70)
    Seminar focused on dual goals of training and research.
  - JCSS - Rockefeller Foundation - International Fellowship Program, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 71)
    International Fellowship Program for the Development of Soviet Studies. Budget and Report on 1988 awards.
  - JCSS - Rockefeller Foundation - International Fellowship Program (Mailing LIsts and Application Requests), 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Joint Committee on Soviet Studies (JCSS) - Chronological Files, 1987 January-June (Box 8, Folder 73-79)
  - Joint Committee on Soviet Studies (JCSS) - Chronological Files, 1987 July - 1988 March 25 (Box 9, Folder 80-88)
  - Joint Committee on Soviet Studies (JCSS) - Chronological Files, 1988 March 26 - September (Box 10, Folder 89-96)
  - Joint Committee on Soviet Studies (JCSS) - Chronological Files, 1988 October-December (Box 11, Folder 97-99)
  - Joint Committee on Soviet Studies (JCSS) - Chronological Files (Membership and Appointments), 1986-1988 (Box 11, Folder 100)
    Letters of appointment to the JCSS and its subcommittees.
  - Joint Committee on Soviet Studies (JCSS) - Chronological Files, 1989 January-March (Box 11, Folder 101-105)
  - Joint Committee on Soviet Studies (JCSS) - Chronological Files, 1989 April-October (Box 12, Folder 106-113)
  - Joint Committee on Soviet Studies (JCSS) - Chronological Files, 1989 November - 1990 August (Box 13, Folder 114-121)
  - Joint Committee on Soviet Studies (JCSS) - Chronological Files, 1990 September - 1991 May (Box 14, Folder 122-130)
  - Joint Committee on Soviet Studies (JCSS) - Chronological Files, 1991 June - 1992 May (Box 15, Folder 131-137)
  - Joint Committee on the Soviet Union and its Successor States (JCSSS) - Chronological Files, 1992 June-October (Box 15, Folder 138-140)
  - Joint Committee on the Soviet Union and its Successor States (JCSSS) - Chronological Files, 1992 November - 1993 February (Box 16, Folder 141-143)
  - Joint Committee on the Soviet Union and its Successor States (JCSSS) - Chronological Files - Fellowship Awards, 1993 February 22 - March 1 (Box 16, Folder 144)
    Award letters for Graduate Training, Dissertation, and Postdoctoral fellowships. Also includes notices for First-Year Fellowship in Underrepresented Fields and for Summer Language Institutes.
  - Joint Committee on the Soviet Union and its Successor States (JCSSS) - Chronological Files - Fellowships (Declinations), 1993 February 25 - March 2 (Box 16, Folder 145)
    Declination letters for Graduate Training, Dissertation, and Postdoctoral fellowships.
  - Joint Committee on the Soviet Union and its Successor States (JCSSS) - Chronological Files, 1993 March-May (Box 16, Folder 146-149)
    March file includes invitations to the Sixth Annual Summer Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics and Society (June 7-18, 1993).
  - Joint Committee on the Soviet Union and its Successor States (JCSSS) - Chronological Files, 1993 June-November (Box 17, Folder 150-154)
  - JCSS - Economics Subcommittee - Meetings and Membership, 1984-1987 (Box 17, Folder 155)
    Includes memos and notes on January 28, 1984 meeting.
  - JCSS - Soviet Economy, 1983-1990 (Box 17, Folder 156)
    Support for the journal Soviet Economy and for a series of panel discussions on the topic.
  - JCSS - Soviet Economy Panel, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 157)
    First Roundtable on the Soviet Economic Outlook, March 7, 1986, Brookings Institution.
  - JCSS - Soviet Economy Panel (Moscow), 1987 (Box 17, Folder 158)
  - JCSS - Soviet Economy Panel, 1988 October (Box 17, Folder 159)
    US - Soviet Roundtable, Washington, DC, October 3-5, 1988.
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - Announcements, 1985-1988 (Box 17, Folder 160)
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - Correspondence and Planning, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 161)
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - Correspondence and Planning, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 162-163)
    First Annual Workshop, University of Illinois, Urbana-Champaign.
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - Papers, 1985 July 7-19 (Box 18, Folder 164-166)
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - Questionnaires, 1985 July 7-19 (Box 18, Folder 167)
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - Report, 1985 July 7-19 (Box 18, Folder 168)
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - Correspondence, Participants, and Planning, 1986 July 6-16 (Box 19, Folder 169)
    Second Annual Workshop, University of Illinois, Urbana-Champaign.
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - Questionnaires, 1986 July 6-16 (Box 19, Folder 170)
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - Report, 1986 July 6-16 (Box 19, Folder 171)
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - Participant Respnses, 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 172)
    Responses to inquiry concerning individual changes in status since the workshops.
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - Correspondence and Planning, 1987 July 12-23 (Box 19, Folder 173-174)
    Third Annual Workshop, Georgetown University, Washington, DC.
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - Faculty, 1987 July 12-23 (Box 19, Folder 175)
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - Questionnaires, 1987 July 12-23 (Box 19, Folder 176)
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - Report (Correspondence and Drafts), 1985-1987 (Box 19, Folder 177)
    Drafts of report on 1985-1987 workshops. Includes draft of proposal for 1987 workshop, and funding requests addressed to the Ford Foundation and the Alfred P. Sloan Foundation.
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - Report, 1985-1987 (Box 19, Folder 178, Box 20, Folder 179)
    Reports and questionnaires for workshops in 1985, 1986, and 1987.
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - Report and MacArthur Foundation Request, 1987 June (Box 20, Folder 180)
    Report on the 1985-1986 workshops (June 1987). MacArthur Foundation approached for funding for 1988-1990 workshops.
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - Correspondence and Planning, 1988 July 10-21 (Box 20, Folder 181)
    Fourth Annual workshop, University of California, Berkeley.
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - Papers, 1988 July 10-21 (Box 20, Folder 182-185)
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - Questionnaires, 1988 July 10-21 (Box 21, Folder 186)
    Fourth Annual Workshop, University of California, Berkeley,
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - Report, 1988 July 10-21 (Box 21, Folder 187)
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - Papers, 1989 July 9-21 (Box 21, Folder 188-191)
    Fifth Annual Workshop, University of California, Berkeley,
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - Report, 1989 July 9-21 (Box 21, Folder 192)
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - Planning and Participants, 1990 July 8-19 (Box 22, Folder 193)
    Sixth Annual Workshop, University of Pittsburgh. Includes schedule, faculty and participant lists, and memos.
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - Planning and Expenses, 1990 July 8-19 (Box 22, Folder 194)
    Sixth Annual Workshop, University of Pittsburgh.
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - Papers, 1990 July 8-19 (Box 22, Folder 195-199)
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - Questionnaires, 1990 July 8-19 (Box 23, Folder 200)
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - Report, 1990 July 8-19 (Box 23, Folder 201)
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - Schedule, Faculty, Participants, 1991 July 7-18 (Box 23, Folder 202)
    Seventh Annual Workshop, University of Pittsburgh.
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - Planning and Arrangements, 1991 July 7-18 (Box 23, Folder 203)
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - Papers, 1991 July 7-18 (Box 23, Folder 204-206)
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - Papers, 1991 July 7-18 (Box 24, Folder 207)
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - Questionnaires, 1991 July 7-18 (Box 24, Folder 208)
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - Report, 1991 July 7-18 (Box 24, Folder 209)
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - General, 1992 July 12-23 (Box 24, Folder 210)
    Eighth Annual Workshop, University of Pittsburgh.
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - Papers, 1992 July 12-23 (Box 24, Folder 211-214)
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - Questionnaires, 1992 July 12-23 (Box 24, Folder 215)
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - Funding Requests, 1986-1988 (Box 25, Folder 216)
    Correspondence with Ford, MacArthur, and other Foundations concerning funding for 1987-1990 workshops.
  - JCSS - Soviet and East European Economics Workshop - Funding Requests, 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 217)